<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://Martinvf88.github.io/blog</id>
    <title>My Site Blog</title>
    <updated>2019-06-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://Martinvf88.github.io/blog"/>
    <subtitle>My Site Blog</subtitle>
    <icon>https://Martinvf88.github.io/img/favicon.ico</icon>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Session №1 - The reunion]]></title>
        <id>first-session</id>
        <link href="https://Martinvf88.github.io/blog/first-session"/>
        <updated>2019-06-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We enter a world one of many that exist in the prime material plane, one named]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>We enter a world one of many that exist in the prime material plane, one named
<code>D&#x27;orbiludum</code>, a medieval-like place, booming with magic but also in the midst
of developing primitive firearms. We change our focus to the continent Bàaxal,
on the Midwestern town of Irkstone. This quaint mid-sized town is located south
of the <code>Meerqer Mountain Range</code>, west of the <code>Ja&#x27;ffay Depths</code> and just touching
the beginning of the <code>Lamiscate fields</code>. It is known to be the &quot;starting points
of adventurers&quot;.</p><p>You? Well you&#x27;re a no-name/local legend band of adventurers, a party known as
<code>Table №5</code>, and while it&#x27;s not your official name it is related to an infamous
event regarding a table, a <strong>lot of ale</strong>, and the <strong>unrestrained rowdyness</strong> of
your <a href="../../../docs/table-5/elber-galarga">Dragonborn Fighter</a> and
<a href="../../../docs/table-5/yaboji">Half-Elf Ranger</a>. </p><p>Though you&#x27;re a dime a dozen, you do have a relatively <em>good-ish</em> reputation in
the city of <code>Irkstone</code>... <em><strong>Somehow</strong></em>.</p><p>Your party, while diverse is known for it&#x27;s lack of humans. You did however have
a human adventurer by your side, a Wizard named Serolf. And though he was an odd
individual, he did work well with you motley lot, but one day he decided to just
retire to study at leisure. Some of you think him dead, others wonder where he
really is.</p><p>The party decided to separate for a few months, and meet up at Irkstone at the
local pub, <code>Trichotillomaniac&#x27;s Ponytail</code>, this name is due to the previous owner
being a pretentious asshole and the current one, <code>Grog Steingut</code>, being too lazy
to properly do the paperwork required to change the name. In any case, folk just
call it <code>The Tricky Pony</code>, which has NOTHING TO DO with the original name.</p><p>The Tricky Pony also serves as the unofficial Guild office, since Grog actually
is the Guild Master the town&#x27;s branch of the Adventurer&#x27;s Guild.</p><p>It is here where our adventure starts.</p>]]></content>
        <author>
            <name>Martín Valencia Flores</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>