<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>Martín Valencia Flores Blog</title>
        <link>https://Martinvf88.github.io/blog</link>
        <description>Martín Valencia Flores Blog</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Session №2 - The Claws of Darkness]]></title>
            <link>https://Martinvf88.github.io/blog/second-session</link>
            <guid>second-session</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[After routing a Goblin attack on the city, you returned to The Tricky Pony, to]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>After routing a Goblin attack on the city, you returned to The Tricky Pony, to
receive your reward and rest. You see old man <code>Bob</code> come into the tavern, and
mid-greeting he turns a sickly shade of blue, as you see a spectral hand rip out
his soul, leaving a husk of a man behind.</p><p><code>Grog</code> immediately recognizes this as a sign that <strong>The Temple</strong>, a sealed, old
research center built over <em>ancient ruins</em>, being active again.</p><p>Being the only adventurers at hand he offers 50 GP for you to investigate, but
insists on you taking the less than friendly <code>wizard Nitram</code>, who was hanging at
the bar and helped in the fight against the Goblins.</p><p>After walking in the direction of <code>Ja&#x27;ffay Depths</code>, you approach the outskirts
of the swampy marshlands. <code>Ione</code> deduces that <code>Nitram</code>, being a <code>wizard</code>, has at
least basic knowledge of this <strong>&quot;Temple&quot;</strong>. He confirms this, and gives her the
general location and an estimated time of arrival, and the party decides to rest.</p><p>After an uneventful night (during which both <code>Ione</code> and <code>Nitram</code> had a barely
civil conversation) you begin to enter the marshland. Almost immediately <code>Ravoo</code>
and <code>Ione</code> notice that the more the party advances, the more <strong>corrupted</strong> the
ecosystem seems to get.</p><p>You&#x27;re suddenly attacked by a swarm of Skeletons, and through luck, experience,
and grit you manage to defeat them all. You decide to take a short rest and as
you are gathering strength and tending to your wounds, 2 wraiths, whose presence
emanates more power and darkness than <em>anyone or anything</em> any of you has ever
encountered, manifest. They conjure a pair of what seem to be hand pistols and
without warning, shoot the at the ground beneath <code>Nitram&#x27;s</code> feet, forming a dark
and arcane sigil.</p><p>The last you see of this <code>Half-elf wizard</code> is his face full of fear and terror,
as he tries to extend a hand towards all of you, just to be grappled by a pair
of <code>ghostly, necrotic green skeletal hands</code> that pull him into the dark abyss,
as he vanishes before your eyes.</p><p>It is here where we reenter our story.</p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Session №1 - The reunion]]></title>
            <link>https://Martinvf88.github.io/blog/first-session</link>
            <guid>first-session</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2019 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[We enter a world one of many that exist in the prime material plane, one named]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We enter a world one of many that exist in the prime material plane, one named
<code>D&#x27;orbiludum</code>, a medieval-like place, booming with magic but also in the midst
of developing primitive firearms. We change our focus to the continent Bàaxal,
on the Midwestern town of Irkstone. This quaint mid-sized town is located south
of the <code>Meerqer Mountain Range</code>, west of the <code>Ja&#x27;ffay Depths</code> and just touching
the beginning of the <code>Lamiscate fields</code>. It is known to be the &quot;starting points
of adventurers&quot;.</p><p>You? Well you&#x27;re a no-name/local legend band of adventurers, a party known as
<code>Table №5</code>, and while it&#x27;s not your official name it is related to an infamous
event regarding a table, a <strong>lot of ale</strong>, and the <strong>unrestrained rowdyness</strong> of
your <a href="../../../docs/table-5/elber-galarga">Dragonborn Fighter</a> and
<a href="../../../docs/table-5/yaboji">Half-Elf Ranger</a>. </p><p>Though you&#x27;re a dime a dozen, you do have a relatively <em>good-ish</em> reputation in
the city of <code>Irkstone</code>... <em><strong>Somehow</strong></em>.</p><p>Your party, while diverse is known for it&#x27;s lack of humans. You did however have
a human adventurer by your side, a Wizard named Serolf. And though he was an odd
individual, he did work well with you motley lot, but one day he decided to just
retire to study at leisure. Some of you think him dead, others wonder where he
really is.</p><p>The party decided to separate for a few months, and meet up at Irkstone at the
local pub, <code>Trichotillomaniac&#x27;s Ponytail</code>, this name is due to the previous owner
being a pretentious asshole and the current one, <code>Grog Steingut</code>, being too lazy
to properly do the paperwork required to change the name. In any case, folk just
call it <code>The Tricky Pony</code>, which has NOTHING TO DO with the original name.</p><p>The Tricky Pony also serves as the unofficial Guild office, since Grog actually
is the Guild Master the town&#x27;s branch of the Adventurer&#x27;s Guild.</p><p>It is here where our adventure starts.</p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>